globalismedia.com 2013-10-16

# Privacy

**Globalis Media Inc. Privacy Policy** ****

Ver. 12/1/2012

This page sets forth the privacy policies and practices of Globalis Media Inc.'s ("Globalis Media") company web site,

[www.globalismedia.com](http://www.valueclick.com/) ("Globalis Media Site"). The information collection practices of all web sites owned by, or served online ads by Globalis Media are detailed by the privacy policies found on such web sites.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully since by visiting this site and sharing information with Globalis Media you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy unless you offer different terms which are accepted by Globalis Media Inc. in writing.

**I. INFORMATION WE COLLECT, CONSUMER CHOICE AND ACCESS**

The Globalis Media Site is not directed towards individual Internet users nor does it seek any personally identifiable information ("PII") from such users for marketing purposes. The only PII that may be collected is when a consumer seeks information from Globalis Media and contacts Globalis Media on his or her own accord by e-mail or through a contact form, written correspondence, or otherwise.

Like most standard web site servers, we use log files to collect Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring/exit pages, platform type, third party web analytic tools, and date/time stamp. We use the information to analyze site usage, administer the site, understand usage and navigation trends in aggregate, and determine the relevance of content.  Globalis Media may use cookies to collect data from this website to enable it to more effectively match advertisements to your interests. 

**II. INFORMATION MANAGEMENT**

Globalis Media may share information with its affiliated entities for or in connection with the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial asset, reorganization or liquidation of Globalis Media or any affiliated companies.  Globalis Media also may release information when we believe release is appropriate to respond to a subpoena or otherwise comply with the law; enforce or apply our agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Globalis Media, its affiliates, and others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

**III. SECURITY**

Globalis Media uses industry standard security measures to ensure the security of data. Globalis Media has contracts in place with its customers in relation to their data, which data is handled in accordance with such agreements or as otherwise agreed upon by such parties.

No transmission of data over the Internet, however, is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of Globalis Media to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect users' information, Globalis Media cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. You acknowledge and assume this risk when communicating with us.  
**IV. CONSENT AND CHANGES**

Globalis Media may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will update the effective date so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.  
  
**V. DATA PROCESSING AND SAFE HARBOR**

The European Union ("EU") maintains strict privacy laws. These rules differ significantly from the laws of the United States of America (“US”). To reconcile these differences, the US and the EU have created a safe harbor (“Safe Harbor”) that defines mutually acceptable privacy operations. For more information see

[www.export.gov/safeharbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/). Globalis Media is neither incorporated in nor operationally based in the US or EU.  However, users based in the US and EU use web sites owned by, managed by, or served online ads by Globalis Media, and Globalis Media endeavors and takes reasonable actions to adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles.   
  
**VI. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY, VENUE, THIRD PARTY INFORMATION & LANGUAGE**

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER THE PRIVACY OF GLOBALIS MEDIA DATA OR GLOBALIS MEDIA'S PRACTICES IS SUBJECT TO THE PROVISIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND ANY APPLICABLE TERMS AND CONDITIONS (WHICH MAY INCLUDE LIMITATIONS ON DAMAGES AND/OR ARBITRATION OF DISPUTES). YOU AGREE THAT GLOBALIS MEDIA'S LIABILITY FOR ANY BREACH OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE GREATER OF THE VALUE OF THE TRANSACTIONS OR SERVICES PROVIDED TO YOU BY GLOBALIS MEDIA OR $100 TO THE EXTENT SUCH CLAIM IS NOT OTHERWISE BARRED BY OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS. YOU FURTHER AGREE THAT THIS AGREEMENT IS GOVERNED BY THE LAWS OF THE REPUBLIC OF THE PHILIPPINES WITHOUT REGARD TO CHOICE OF LAW PRINCIPLES AND THAT ANY ACTION ARISING FROM OR RELATED TO THIS POLICY WILL BE PURSUED EXCLUSIVELY IN THE VENUE OF CEBU CITY, CEBU PROVINCE, REPUBLIC OF THE PHILIPPINES.

You also agree that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose personal data you supply to Globalis Media with regard to: (a) the purposes for which such third party's personal data has been collected; (b) the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party's personal data; (c) which of the third party's data are obligatory and which data, if any, are voluntary; and (d) how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the data held about them. It is the express will of the parties that this agreement and all related documents have been drawn up in English.

**CONTACT US**

For more information or if you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via the button below.  Alternatively, you may send written correspondence to the following address: Globalis Media Inc., Att: Privacy Dept., Keppel Center #205, Cebu Business Park, Cebu City 6000, Philippines.

 Privacy Inquiry
